I know this video message is
specifically to Chris for from special
books for special kids I'm so sorry your
comment section got to leave it off with
YouTube I think that is horrible and I
only came across your channel like a
month ago and I'm so excited I've been
telling people about it it is amazing I
love falling in love with the kids and
adults that you interview please keep
doing what you're doing
but when listened to you talk about
what's happening with YouTube I had a
somewhat of a solution come to mind
which is in no way helping with youtube
because their corporation and they seem
to have policies that are broken and so
I don't know how to fix that
my solution what I'm here on the planet
to do with my health challenges is to
create the democratic transparent
technologic company that we all own
together we can create things like a
YouTube that we own that we can decide
how it's monetized and we can make
logical conclusions of like here's a
blanket rule but that's not what I'm
saying is their solution that's gonna
take a longer time I'm often very
saddened by the fact that there are
people on this planet who don't have
friends and don't have connection
whether that's because they're they
can't find the people they connect with
or because they have have health
challenges that they look different
whatever the reason is I think that a
friendship like a site designed
specifically for that purpose a site
that isn't YouTube that is designed to
so that the little girl you interviewed
that is nine and going through cancer
and can't find friends at her school can
have a like dating site to find actual
friends where people can can support
each other a whole entire site is
created so that that's the case because
neurotypical kids right all kids need
help finding friends and so to be able
to facilitate that so that everyone can
find a place and everyone can have a
friends and everyone can have community
I have ideas on how to create that but I
don't have the means right now to
physically do it I'm in the process of
creating community to be able to do the
big the big thing the big net Netflix of
apps that we collectively owned
but I would be willing to work on this
but it's it's not I don't know what I
would have to offer besides the exact
idea which is a dating site for kids to
find their to find friends and possibly
even a fan base site for like your the
people you interview and everyone
because what I do see when I see people
on your site is like oh I love Ruby and
I love but there's like millions of
other ones out there who will never be
on your channel anyway and as I'm sure
you would agree they're equally
deserving of connection enough having
the world see them and everyone's
everyone is is worthy of that and if we
can create anyone can create a site that
is designed so that we can facilitate
that process in a safe and caring way
what my view is always bringing those
people together to create that instead
of doing it behind closed doors but I
would love to chat with you and offer
anything that I that I could offer in
that regard and potentially work through
a process of that being our first
project that we'll own collectively
together if that interests you were
doing it all on your own in a for-profit
or not-for-profit I just want it to
exist in the world
I just want children to be able to find
community and I want your work to be
what it is which is powerful and amazing
and I will end this year thanks